{
    "id": "83d2875813884e2facb36582cb1c4495",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… call you tonight.",
            "description": "We use will in promises.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The contractor …………………………. be responsible for the maintenance of the building and its premises.",
            "description": "In contracts, shall is often used with third person subjects to refer to obligations and duties. Will be also possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… give you a laptop for your birthday.",
            "description": "Both will and shall can be used with first person subjects in promises.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What time ………………………. I come and see you?",
            "description": "We use shall to ask for instructions and decisions.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What on earth ……………………….. we do?",
            "description": "We use shall to ask for instructions and decisions.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "may",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… I get something to eat?",
            "description": "We use shall to ask for instructions and decisions.",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Make me a cup of tea, ………………………….. you?",
            "description": "We use will to give instructions and orders.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I promise I …………………….. tell lies again.",
            "description": "We use will in promises.",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "shouldn't",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… kill you if you do that again.",
            "description": "We use will in threats.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… I carry your bag?",
            "description": "We use shall to ask for instructions.",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Shall"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Can somebody help me?’ ‘I ……………………’",
            "description": "We use will to express our willingness to do things.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. the train be on time?",
            "description": "We use will to talk about simple futurity. ",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}